No one would deliberately kill Joyce.
Right, Director Phil?
I know you think I was behind what happened.
I didn't say anything like that.
Maybe the police are just overly suspicious
of everyone.
It's just a simple case of neglect.
There's no one to blame but me.
I insisted on working with her.
I'm recording myself right now.
This is about the suspect, Lando.
And his boss, Congressman Ramon dela Peña.
Put your hands up.
Freeze! You're under arrest.
Tell me.
You have nothing to do with it. Right?
Joyce...
What kind of life is this?
I don't know if this is a curse.
I was given a typewriter to change our lives.
But things only got worse...
And it led to this tragedy.
I'm tired of blaming the world.
I'm tired of blaming the typewriter.
Because I know...
from the beginning...
that there's no one to blame but me.
Joyce, sorry.
Sorry.
I love you so much.
I love you so much...
Ever since the beginning...
Even back in our old world...
I love you.
I love you so much too.
So much.
Until this present time,
I still love you so much.
I'm also happy working with you.
Wait, where is this conversation headed?
I love you.
If I will be given a chance...
To change everything again...
I would do the right thing.
Even though it hurts.
I would stay away from you.
I will let you be happy.
Even if I'm not the one you're with.
I love you so much, Joyce.
Hey!
Hey, stop!
Stop it!
Move!
Intoy?
Move! I'm going to hit you.
- I said move.
- You're so stubborn.
Sir, wait, wait.
- What's going on here?
- Hey, Bro.
They want to arrest me,
but I'm not doing anything wrong.
What are you talking about?
You've been told not to stay there.
You're stubborn.
What happened?
Bro, I was just scavenging
for junk I could sell.
You heard him, Sir.
Sir, I'll take care of him. I know Intoy.
Fine, just make sure
he won't return to our neighborhood.
Yes, Sir. I got it.
Hey, Bro.
Is that really you, Bro?
"Hey Bro", my foot.
I've been looking for you, Intoy.
Where were you?
Thank you, Bro.
I would have been arrested
if it wasn't for you.
What are you doing here, anyway?
Why are you here?
I visited Joyce.
Savana.
Oh, yeah.
I broke down and cried when I saw the news.
May she rest in peace.
Intoy, I'd love to talk to you more,
but I have an important thing to do.
What is it, Bro?
Something that I should have done before.
I need to do what's right.
Okay, Bro.
I'll just give you something before you go.
Sorry, Bro. This is all I can give you.
Please accept it.
Intoy, no. You need this more.
Come on, Bro. Please accept it.
So I can be a good friend to you too somehow.
Go on, Bro. Don't say no.
Thank you, Intoy.
Here, Bro.
You might choke.
Intoy, what's this?
Where did you get this typewriter?
I've been looking for this.
What are you going to do, Bro?
I need to write something.
Is that the important thing you have to do?
No, no, no.
This is different.
This is more important than that.
Is that the "right thing"
you're talking about?
Intoy, I don't care
whether it's wrong or right.
Bro, even if there's a price to pay?
What are you talking about?
- Bro, don't use that. That's mine.
- Intoy, stop!
- Bro, that's mine!
- Intoy, this is mine!
- You just found it. This is mine!
- Bro, don't!
I've been looking for this, Intoy.
Stop. Bro, don't do it.
- This is mine!
- Bro, that's mine.
- Intoy!
- Bro!
This is mine.
Bro, you don't know what you're doing.
Bro...
Please shut up, Intoy.
Bro!
Bro, what are you writing?
For the second time,
I brought tragedy to your life, my love.
Bro, I said stop it!
Bro!
Bro, it can't correct all your mistakes.
What do you mean, Intoy?
Sorry, I was stubborn.
I love you so much.
Sorry for getting stuck
in my messy life again.
I feel like I killed you.
I want to bring your life back.
I wish you didn't know
about Congressman Ramon dela Peña's
evil doings.
And you didn't get dragged
into all this mess.
Brace yourself, Bro!
It always comes with a price!
You could have been alive today, Joyce.
No one should use the typewriter!
It has a curse.
Intoy!
Joyce, hang in there.
4:46 AM, time of death.
The suspect, Congressman Ramon dela Peña.
I love you, Joyce.
[Write Here Waiting]
I know.
True.
- Sir Liam.
- Sir Liam, let's take a picture.
This is it.
Sir Liam, congrats!
Liam, this is it.
Everyone is so excited.
Oh, boy. I'm so excited.
We're about to see it.
My God. You really are something, Phil.
This will be a blockbuster.
Sir Liam, congratulations.
Hi, Director Phil. Congratulations!
Congrats to us.
Love.
What's up with your face? We should smile.
It's your big day.
What's happening?
Please understand my boyfriend.
It seems that it hasn't sunk in yet
that we're about to premiere the film
we all worked hard for.
Congrats.
Social media is exploding.
So I'm sure this will be a hit.
Congrats.
Thanks to Joyce.
Despite what happened to us in the past,
she still trusted me.
Love... I know how you feel.
That's how I am
every time Escale releases a new issue.
Don't worry.
All you have to do is smile and project.
Everything's going to be alright.
- Joyce is here!
- Joyce...
Joyce.
Oh my god.
Oh my God.
Your story has once again changed, Liam.
I'm sure there is a price to pay.
Thank you.
Hello.
Congratulations.
Joyce.
Hi!
- Hi, guys. Good evening.
- Hello.
- You're so beautiful.
- Thank you.
So, Joyce, we have a few questions.
Is it okay?
We know
you've done quite a lot of love stories.
My question is...
How different is this film
from the previous ones you did?
Well, in this film,
we showed the concept of a second chance.
When we hear of second chance,
we think of new love.
But for me, honestly,
a second chance means...
a chance to love ourselves.
Once you're whole,
that's when you can truly love.
That's very well said.
How about in real life?
Is it still self-love for you?
Sorry, it's a bit awkward for me
because Joyce usually is the one
who answers those kinds of questions,
but...
I guess it's time...
that I man up.
Oh my God!
Girlfriend proposal!
Girlfriend proposal.
This is crazy, girls!
Oh my God.
Will you be my girlfriend?
Yes.
Joyce.
Joyce...
Should I keep waiting or...
Are you rejecting my feelings?
Hans...
After everything
that happened the past week...
I saw and realized that in the past years,
no one else stayed by my side but you.
You, who's waiting for me.
You, who's putting up with my moods.
You, who's always there when I have problems.
It's only you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry,
I don't want to be your girlfriend.
Oh, that hurts.
Because...
I want to be your wife.
This is a lot!
Congratulations!
Joyce, I love you.
I love you.
Oh my God!
And now it's official.
The then-rumored
non-showbiz boyfriend of Joyce
is not just her official boyfriend now.
He's already her fiancé!
And, of course,
we look forward to their wedding.
Oh, dear. I'm so thrilled.
I feel like fainting.
My god. This is so thrilling.
I feel like fainting, friend.
- My god, what happened?
- Love?
Love!
It's beautiful.
You know how to pick a good ring.
Son!
- Liam.
- Love.
Are you okay now?
We wanted to bring you to the hospital.
But the medic said it's just over fatigue.
Why don't you sit down.
Oh, son.
Did you know I even dressed up?
Only to find out
I need to look after my child
when I got to your event?
You know,
I think it's because he's been too busy.
You haven't had enough sleep
because you're busy preparing
for the premiere night, right?
We'll let you sleep.
You should get some rest.
Son, how are you?
Do you want some medicine?
No, I'm okay.
Liam, you missed a lot.
Too bad you didn't see
how people applauded our film.
I was so happy.
So happy and overwhelmed.
Are you happy
only because of the success of the movie, babe?
Of course, I'm so happy
because of this too, babe.
Oh, boy. I'm so happy for you, Joyce, Hans.
Congratulations to the both of you.
Thank you.
Gosh.
Me, too.
Congrats again, guys.
Let's celebrate?
Cheers!
- Cheers.
Congratulations.
Son...
Are you okay, Liam?
Of course.
We're together,
and we fulfilled our dreams...
through this movie project.
So I don't see any reason to be...
unhappy.
If I could have a chance...
A chance to change everything again,
I would do the right thing.
Even if it hurts.
I will stay away from you.
I will let you be happy...
Even if you're with someone else.
So...
Good luck with your next movie.
Why does it feel
like you're saying goodbye to me?
Don't you want to work with me anymore?
Liam...
I'm so happy...
that the whole world will see
the film we worked hard for...
Except for my father.
Why?
What happened to Uncle Edmond?
Are you serious?
Are you really asking me
what happened to my father?
Are you really awake, Liam?
I'm sorry, Joyce.
Sorry, maybe...
Maybe you're still confused.
My dad...
He became blind, remember?
Blind?
Yeah.
He had...
My father had another episode
inside the wellness center.
I don't know what triggered it.
And the rehab couldn't explain
why my father had access
to their medical storage room.
My dad...
He overdosed on quinine.
A malaria medicine.
Maybe he just took whatever he grabbed.
After a few hours, his eyesight got affected.
The doctor said
there was nothing we could do.
Joyce...
It's so sad.
It's sad because...
Because my father was there with me...
back in the cinema.
He was beside me.
But he couldn't see anything.
It hurts.
It hurts me because...
no matter how many films I make...
Even if I do my best
in my succeeding films...
He can no longer see them.
Joyce, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for what happened to Uncle Edmond.
Hey, join us.
Oh, sorry.
Why do you always spend time together?
Although...
I feel I need to get some rest now.
We have to be early tomorrow, Love.
What's happening tomorrow?
Didn't Borj remind you
of your schedule tomorrow?
We have a meeting with my dad.
Come on.
It's for his candidacy.
He's running for Senate, remember?
He hired you.
You will do his campaign ads.
Are you okay?
[Edmond, Father of Joyce Trinidad]
[Edmond Trinidad,
father of famous actress Joyce Trinidad,]
[went blind due to drug overdose]
The story behind what happened to you
isn't convincing, Uncle Edmond.
I'm the only one who knows
that there might be another reason
for what happened to you.
So?
How are you feeling?
Maybe you fainted
because you're so stressed out.
I'm okay, Mom.
Don't worry about me.
But I'm happy for you, son.
Now that you got everything you want,
what's your next step?
I don't want to make a mistake, Mom.
I don't want to.
My son...
Come on.
I'm just asking you about your plans.
And you're already worried
about something else.
Liam, son, people make mistakes.
You're not human if you don't make mistakes.
But, Mom...
Whenever I try
to correct the mistakes I made,
things don't turn out how I want them to be.
You have to stand firm...
especially by the decisions you make.
You have to face the consequences
of your decision.
Son...
What is it, son?
What are you looking at?
It's nothing, Mom.
You should get some rest.
It's late.
You're the one who fainted.
You should be the one resting.
You're so silly.
Go on. I got this.
Are you sure?
Okay. Go to bed early, okay?
I will.
Good night, Mom.
I'm glad you accepted my offer
to give our friendship a second chance, Liam.
But I will make it clear to you, Liam.
Don't use your obsession with second chances
as a theme for my campaign series.
Why would I need a second chance?
I'm not doing anything wrong.
Second chances are only for the weak.
For people who always make mistakes.
That's why they're asking
for a second chance.
And that's not me.
What we need to communicate to the voters,
is I will continue
the good things I've started.
And this time, we take it to the next level.
Something that
will make people look up to me.
We will set the bar pretty high
so no one can beat us.
Yes, Dad.
Don't worry.
I'll make sure
Liam will implement your directions
in the campaign accordingly.
I'll take care of it. Okay?
Sorry, I have to go. I need to do something.
Love.
Let's talk later.
Hans.
Thank you for meeting with me.
I just want to know
what happened to your investigation
of the death
of a Casa Fuerte construction worker.
Siloy?
Liam.
You know
that the cases I handle are confidential.
But I'm wondering.
Why are you interested in this case?
What's going on, Liam?
Because I know...
you suspect
that Casa Fuerte is involved in Siloy's death.
Is that right?
Maybe that's why I don't want
to tell you anything, Liam.
Because your family might be involved.
What's your motive, Liam?
What do you want?
Hans...
I'm willing to work with you.
So that we can give justice
to Siloy's death and Uncle Edmond's blindness.
How did Uncle Edmond get involved?
What do you know?
Come to think of it, Liam,
when Joyce told me
that Uncle Edmond knew the suspect,
he overdosed before I could talk to him.
What do you think?
Was there foul play?
That what happened to Uncle Edmond
was not self-inflicted?
Thank goodness.
There he is.
Your father has been waiting for you, son.
He even brought cake.
But I'm on a diet.
That's not for you.
I brought it for Liam.
I dropped by to congratulate you.
Your movie is so successful.
I'm so proud of you.
Of course, you're proud,
because the film is making profits.
You think about nothing else but money.
Is that how your mother talks to you, too?
We have lots of vacant rooms at home.
You might want to move in.
My son is not coming with you.
I'll kill if I have to.
I've been telling your father to leave.
I told him to go to Casa Fuerte
so he could talk to you.
He said he would wait for you.
Look.
Why?
What if I want to see you, too?
Whatever.
I'm leaving.
I'll take this cake.
Dad.
I know I already asked you this...
But please tell me the truth.
What do you know about Siloy's death?
And about Lando,
the Congressman's right-hand man?
Are you still working with them?
Can you not ask me such questions?
Ramon already set me free.
I will no longer work for him.
He even let go of Casa Fuerte and Blacksmith.
Ramon will run for Senator.
So the money he makes in our companies
is no longer enough.
Our companies are already free.
Vergil is now the CEO of Casa Fuerte.
Now, you can make films as much as you want.
[Incoming call: Joyce]
Dad, excuse me.
Okay.
Hello, Joyce.
Liam, where are you?
You're the only one missing here.
Okay.
Liam...
It's time for you to do what's right.
We've lived in sin.
- Congratulations!
- Boss Bro.
Congratulations!
Congrats on our movie's success.
Right?
- Cheers.
- Thank you so much, everyone.
I'm so glad
to see you all happy and complete.
To many more successful projects!
Cheers!
Cheers, Sir!
There's no such thing as a perfect life.
Something challenging and painful
always happens.
I'm slowly accepting
what happened to my father.
Now I can say that I have no regrets.
I know I'm content.
What are we waiting for?
Party, party!
Let's party!
Congratulations!
Of course, congratulations everyone.
Shot, shot, shot.
To all the hardworking staff,
congratulations to you all.
Uncle Edmond.
I know that voice.
Liam.
Yes, Uncle.
One of the things I learned
from what happened to me,
is that there may be things
the eyes can't see,
but the heart will hear it.
You're sad.
No, I'm not.
If you have a problem, don't be shy.
You can come to me. We can talk.
You're like a family to me.
Thank you.
Congratulations on your film.
My daughter is content.
A heartfelt thanks to you.
Joyce has fulfilled her dream.
Thank you so much, Uncle.
Great job! Great!
Your voice is great.
It can't just be me.
Boss Bro, please sing for us.
Yes, that's right.
DJ, please play the song "Oras".
It's better if you sing too, girl.
Girl, let's go!
This way.
Let's give them a round of applause!
- You do it.
- You can do it.
- I don't want to sing.
- You can't say no.
- This is embarrassing.
- You're the heroes, right?
You can do it.
Can we do this?
I don't know.
Okay, let's try.
You go first?
Me first?
You can do it.
This is embarrassing.
♫ In our one year together ♫
♫ Everything I dreamed of came true ♫
♫ A whole month seemed to disappear ♫
♫ Whenever I was with you,
oh, how quickly time flew ♫
♫ And if only I could go back to the past ♫
♫ I would make sure I never hurt you ♫
♫ Every day, I regret ♫
♫ Letting things turn out this way ♫
♫ If only I had known
this was where we would end ♫
♫ I would have cherished
every hour I spent with you ♫
Thank you.
My friend is so great!
Guys, hello. Congratulations.
- Babe.
- Odet.
Babe, hello.
Hi, Babe. I thought...
Uncle.
Babe, I thought you couldn't make it.
I finished early.
So, here I am. How are you?
Are you having fun?
Of course. Have you eaten yet?
Not yet. I'm hungry.
Don't worry. I'll fix you a plate.
Okay. Thank you.
Liam... Why aren't you answering my calls?
I thought you are willing to work with me?
You think someone turned Uncle blind, right?
Who is it? Who do you have in mind?
Forget everything I said, Attorney.
I don't know anything.
Everything is fine.
Let's not cause trouble.
- Wait.
- Babe, what...
Joyce. Joyce, hang in there.
Joyce, hang in there, okay?
4:46 AM, time of death.
Liam?
I didn't mean it. Joyce, forgive me.
Liam, what are you doing?
What sin are you talking about?
Liam, what was it that I saw?
You're the man in my dreams.
You're using a typewriter.
There's something you always tell me
in my dreams...
That you did something wrong.
I don't understand. Why is it like that?
Why does it feel like it really happened?
We were shooting a scene in our film,
and then...
I saw I was shot.
I felt that I died.
I saw it. It felt real.
I was shot. I died.
It felt like it really happened.
I died.
Promise me this.
You will protect my daughter.
You might be dealing
with an influential person.
And I don't want my daughter to get involved.
I love your daughter so much.
Rest in power. Stefano Lualhati.
What?
- I can't understand you.
- Liam, what are you doing?
What am I doing?
Tell me, what's happening? Where's Sep?
That night, we heard him screaming.
And when we got out,
we saw him on the road, unconscious.
The surrounding smelled like gasoline.